A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Health Care in New York City Program, SG 3, Series 2 FA1459
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Health Care in New York City Program, SG 3, Series 2
1993-1998
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1459
1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter-size document boxes
Arrangement
Records remain in original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
This series documents the grant administration files and associated program files for the Commonwealth Fund Health Care in New York City program. Each grant file often contains records pertaining to: budget and administration, proposals and development, articles and background information, correspondence, grant products and related files. The resulting Louis Harris and Associates survey is also included.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was transferred to RAC as accession 2007:077.
- New York City Survey - Questionnaire Development (96003), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- New York State - Low Income and Access to Care Survey, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Louis Harris and Associates - New York City Health Care Survey (96003), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- New York City Survey - Consultants, Leaders, Foundations, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Louis Harris and Associates - New York City Health Care Survey (96003) - Articles and Background (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Louis Harris and Associates - New York City Health Care Survey (96003) - Administration and Budget, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Louis Harris and Associates - New York City Health Care Survey (96003) - Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Louis Harris and Associates - New York City Health Care Survey (96003) - Grant Products (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Louis Harris and Associates - New York City Health Care Survey (96003) - Grant Products - Managed Care and Access to Health Care in New York City, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Global Strategy Group - Feld - Examining Enrollment Barriers for Uninsured Children in New York City (980519) - Articles and Background, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Global Strategy Group - Feld - Examining Enrollment Barriers for Uninsured Children in New York City (980519) - Proposal Development, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Global Strategy Group - Feld - Examining Enrollment Barriers for Uninsured Children in New York City (980519) - Administration and Budget, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Global Strategy Group - Feld - Examining Enrollment Barriers for Uninsured Children in New York City (980519) - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Global Strategy Group - Feld - Examining Enrollment Barriers for Uninsured Children in New York City (980519) - Grant Products, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Focus Groups (980519), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Global Strategy Group - Feld - Examining Enrollment Barriers for Uninsured Children in New York City (980519) - Harris Recontacts, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted - Confidential material.
- Ninth Annual Symposium on Health Services Research in New York, 1998 December 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Focus Groups (980519) - Expert Advisory Meetings, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)